Bartłomiej Cupiał

I am Machine Learning passionate. What drives me the most is to gain a better understanding of how intelligence and consciousness work, mainly by studying deep learning but recently also by reinforcement learning. My main areas of research is unsupervised and reinforcement learning, continual learning and improving the learning efficiency.

⊠ bartlomiej.cupial@gmail.com

505779373

Wrocław, Poland

in linkedin.com/in/username

EDUCATION

Wrocław University of Science and Technology

BSc in Computer Science

2016.10 - 2020.02

WORK EXPERIENCE

Machine Learning Engineer

LifeFlow - main project

- Responsible for design and implementation of machine learning based solutions for cardiac diagnostics problems.
- Developed computer vision algorithms applied to medical data.
- Working with voxels and meshes.
- Using Python, PyTorch, ONNX, Docker, AzureML

2019.11 - Present

LifeFlow - research project

- Research and development reinforcement learning algorithms in cardiac diagnostics.
- Using Python, PyTorch, PyTorch Lightning

2021.01 - Present

C++ developer in starter program Asseco

2019.07 - 2019.10

PROJECTS

Reinforcement Learning algoritmhs for pong game and MuJoCo (2020.10 - 2020.11)

- Small projects coded during Stanford RL course
- Used PyTorch, openai gym, MuJoCo environment
- Implemented DQN and Dueling DQN for pong and Vanilla Policy Gradient, TRPO, PPO for MuJoCo

Machine Learning analysys of network simulations (2020.03 - 2020.09)

- The goal of the project was to learn about GNNs and how they can be used in finding inconsistency problems in graphs.
- Used PyTorch, Pytorch lightning
- Implementing Graph Consis paper, supervising Solvro ML team

My Engineering Thesis (2019)

- Topic: Methods of camera recognition based on image samples
- Used machine learning methods

My own implementation mix match algorithm (2019.06)

Used PyTorch and fastai

SKILLS

Python C++

Git

Linux

Docker O

ORGANIZATIONS

Solvro Students' Association (2018 – Present)

LANGUAGES

Polish English
Native B2/C1

ADDITIONAL EXPERIENCE

Stanford reinforcement learning course

Conducting workshops for new people insterested in machine learning in Solvro Students' Association

MLinPL students speaker (2019 Conference) Talk about MixMatch

Fastai course by n-weaves

Participation in few kaggle contests

Hopelt Hackaton

INTERESTS

Machine and Deep Learning

Chess

Basketball

I hereby give consent for my personal data included in my application to be processed for the purposes of the recruitment process under the Personal Data Protection Act as of 29 August 1997, consolidated text: Journal of Laws 2016, item 922 as amended.